Guide to the Nineteenth Century Notebooks, Diaries, and Journals MC.31
New York University Archives
- Series VIII, John Torrey, 1883, 1938
  Series VIII contains a diary of John Torrey while he was traveling abroad in Europe. Included in this diary are references to his "natural system" of botanical classification.
  - Catalogue of North American Plants, 1833 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - User Copy of Torrey's Diary, 1833 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pages Removed From Diary During Preservation Treatment, 1833 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Letters Concerning Torrey Material, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series IX, Howard Crosby, 1886
  Series IX consists of one journal, which contains sermons written by Howard Crosby.
  - The Revelation of Saint John: Sermons by Howard Crosby, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 7)